# **Azizul Hakim**

# Computer Science Student



# **©** CAREER OBJECTIVE

Third year Computer Science student seeking to use my academic knowledge in a fulltime position. Possess more than 2 year of handson experience building and testing programs in different languages like Java, C++, C and JavaScript. Also have the knowledge of computer hardware (adjusting, repairing and replacing parts). A motivated individual with strong communication skills and problemsolving skills.



### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Banquet Server**

Era Bistro and Catering, Winnipeg, MB / Jan 2018-Present

Delivering exceptional, fast and friendly customer service.

### Server and Bartender

University of Manitoba Catering Services, Winnipeg, MB / Mar 2019–Present

Interacting with customers, taking orders and serving snacks and drinks.

## **Voluntary Math Tutor**

Frontier College, Winnipeg, MB / Sep 2017-Apr 2018

- Assisting kids from grades (1-8) with their homework.
- Improving their ideas on Math and maintaining a friendly relationship with the students.

### **Sustainability Ambassador**

University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, MB / Sep 2019-present

- Volunteer in many different sustainable events.
- Provide information to everyone on campus about sustainability and Sustainable resources.

### Certification

### **Technical Support Fundamental**

- Assemble a computer from scratch
- Choose and install an operating system on a computer
- Learn how applications are created and how they work under the hood of a computer
- Utilize common problem-solving methodologies and soft skills in an Information Technology setting



# **CONTACT**

#### **Email:**

koushikrakib@gmail.com

#### Phone:

2048991451

#### Address:

134-150 Baylor Avenue, Winnipeg, MB

#### Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/azizul-hakim-41862b1a2/

#### Github:

github.com/AzizulHakim96



# PROJECTS

Connect4 game in Java

**Online ordering System** 

**Student Help Portal** 

**Personal Website** 



# HARD SKILLS

Java, C, C++, SQL,

JavaScript, Python, HTML,

CSS, Linux, Lc-3 Assembly,

Microsoft Office, Aws,

Data Entry



### **EDUCATION**

#### **B.S. / COMPUTER**

**SCIENCE** University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, Manitoba 2017-2022